He we are just going to load the autosave file as an example, it was saved when making the FTP demo video...
Here it will just take a few seconds to load... The renderer loads every 250 packets via the preprocessor in chunks...
So the user can start interacting with packets before the preprocessor finishes.
Here we would initially load into list view, but its going to jump to Stats view becuase that is where the autosave was left off.
Here I'm going to load all FTP management packets by clicking it under the Stats tab, where protocols in the capture will appear.
We can review the packet data here on the Host Data tab, but from here I'm going to jump back to the List tab...
This is the List tab, showing all packets in order as they appear in the capture by default, but the columns are, of course, sortable, by clicking the heading.
From here you can also export any of this under the mouse "in context" to the Notes tab.
But instead I'm going to load up another packet from the FTP management stream, so I can show you what it looks like...
in the Conv tab.  We're loading this entire stream, so multiple packets will be loaded into the conversion workspace, back to back.
But you can also load a packet, payload, or the payload from a decoded protocol, such as HTTP into the Conv tab, using the Context Menu, as well.
This what a stream looks like in the Conv tab, or conversions workspace.  As you can see you can also has the payload, or decode the currently loaded protocol.
From here, it looks like it may have captured some credentials, if we got lucky, so lets hop onto the Keystore tab, and check out if it aquired anything...
Oh wow, looks like it captured two usernames and their associated passwords from the FTP management stream! Lets take a peek..
Looks like it grabbed a password for the user "user1", and a password for "anonymous" when they logged in, thats cool.
Lets highlight that password to put it into context, so we can easily put it in the Notes tab, then we can refer to it later on.
Here's the notes tab, pretty basic, you can colorcode your notes too.
Lets get back over to the List tab, so we can view the FTP-DATA stream, which is where our file is.
We can use PacketSnitch's file carving features to rip whatever file the user transferred out of the FTP-DATA stream, so here goes....
If you need to, just check the log to see where it saved the data...
Finally, lets save our session as something memorable so we can load it again!
Hope you had fun following along in this PacketSnitch demo!!!